(Leonard(on board boat, at a party, dancing):)Excuse me, ladies,
but my pants are buzzing.
North Sea, how can I "kelp" you?
(Penny:)-Leonard?
-Penny?
Hey, ifs Penny.
Everybody say "Hi" to Penny.
(Everybody:)Hi, Penny!
Ha! Sounds like you're
having a good time.
Best time of my life!
-isn't it 5:30 in the morning there?
-Is it?
(Leonard:)Hey, everybody,
it's 5:30 in the morning!
(Penny:)Okay, well, we were just calling you
because we were missing you.
(Random voice:)-Iceberg!
-Oh! Hang on.
(Sheldon:)-Are you in danger?
-No, it's a drinking game.
(Leonard:)Whenever we see an iceberg,
we take a shot!
(Everybody:)Berg! Berg!
Berg! Berg! Berg! Berg!
Leonard? Leonard?
(Penny:)I cannot believe we
were missing that jerk.
(Sheldon:)You were.